[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create this eSports logo
如何创建此电子竞技标志
using Inkscape version 1.0 and it's
使用Inkscape 1.0版，它的
important that you use version 1.0 for
重要的是，您使用版本1.0来
this tutorial because we will be using
本教程，因为我们将使用
the new offset live path effect quite a
新的Offset Live Path效果相当不错
bit in this lesson and it's also
在这一课中有一点，它也是
important that you download and install
重要信息：您需要下载并安装
a particular font known as Falcons I
一种被称为猎鹰I的特殊字体
will have that linked in the description
将在描述中链接这一点
of the video it is a free font so go
视频的字体是免费的，所以去吧
ahead and download and install that font
然后下载并安装该字体
before you launch Inkscape and you'll be
在你推出Inkscape之前，你会
good to go and before we get started if
好了，在我们开始之前，如果
you would like to learn more about
您想了解更多有关
Inkscape be sure to check out my
Inkscape一定要查看我的
Inkscape masterclass it's a collection
Inkscape大师类它是一个集合
of over 60 videos where I go over every
有60多个视频，我每看一遍
single tool and feature in Inkscape and
Inkscape和中的单一工具和功能
I explain what it is and demonstrate how
我解释了它是什么，并演示了如何
it works I'll put a link in the
它起作用了，我会放一个链接在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out so we'll get started here
看看这个，我们就从这里开始
in Inkscape the first thing we want to
在Inkscape中，我们首先要做的是
do is setup our documents that we're all
我们要做的就是设置我们所有人的文件
working with this similar layout the
使用这种类似的布局，
first thing I want to do is come up here
我想做的第一件事就是到这里来
and click this button to disable
并单击此按钮以禁用
snapping I want this all disabled for
抓拍，我希望这一切都被禁用
the time being we'll be enabling it
目前，我们将使其成为可能
throughout the tutorial but for now we
贯穿整个教程，但现在我们
want that turned off we're gonna come up
想把它关掉，我们就上来了
here to where it says view view we're
在这里到它所说的查看视图我们在
gonna want custom selected and I'm going
我想要定制选择，我要走了
to go to zoom I'm going to zoom in at 1
要转到缩放模式，我要在1点放大
to 1 and for now we're gonna want the
到1，现在我们想要
alignment distribute menu opened we're
对齐分发菜单已打开，我们正在
gonna want last selected chosen from
我想要最后一次选择
that drop-down then we want the fill and
该下拉菜单，然后我们需要填充和
Stroke menu open which is this button
笔划菜单打开这是哪个按钮
over here or you could press control
在这里，或者你可以按下控制键
shift + F and let me just expand that so
Shift+F，让我来扩展一下
that I have both of these open at the
我把这两个都打开了
same time I just want to change the way
同时我只想改变我的方式
that those menus are Doc's there we go
那些菜单就是医生，我们走吧
and we're gonna use the path effects
我们将使用路径效果
menu too but I'll get to that a little
菜单也有，但我稍后会讲到的。
later so what we want to do now is
所以我们现在要做的是
basically what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
基本上我要做的是我要
break this up into three different parts
把它分成三个不同的部分
and I'll have them time stamped down
我会记下他们的时间
below because this is this is somewhat
下面是因为这是这是有点
of an elaborate design so it's gonna
精心设计，所以它会
take us a while to create this and the
我们需要一些时间来创建这个和
first part will create the text the
第一部分将创建文本
second part will create the emblem and
第二部分将制作会徽和
then in the third part will create the
然后在第三部分中创建
controller so let's start off with the
控制器，所以让我们从
text I'm gonna grab the text tool and
文本我要抓起文本工具
I'm gonna click on the canvas here and
我要点击这里的画布
I'm gonna use all caps for this tutorial
在本教程中，我将使用全部大写字母
I'm going to use the word eSports for
我要用电子竞技这个词来形容
example grab the grab the text tool
示例抓取抓取文本工具
I'm going to change that grab the text
我要改变一下，抓起文本
editor up here I'm gonna change this to
编辑在这里，我要把这个改成
Falcons there we go that's the font
猎鹰在那里，我们走，这是字体
we're looking for let me grab the Select
我们要找的是让我拿上精选
tool and hold ctrl and shift to scale
工具并按住Ctrl键并按比例移动
this up what we want to do now is
这是我们现在想要做的
manually adjust the spacing between
手动调整间距
these letters and I also want to change
这些信和我也想改一下
the way that these letters interact with
这些字母相互作用的方式
each other let me show you what I mean
彼此让我告诉你我的意思
here on the thumbnail if you see here
在缩略图上，如果你看到这里
between these letters you'll see I have
在这些信中，你会看到我有
the letters kind of look like they fit
这些字母看起来很适合
next to each other like puzzle pieces I
就像拼图一样紧挨着我
want to make it so that each letter is
我想让每一个字母都是
slicing off the top right edge of the
切开屏幕右上边缘
letter that comes before it so to do
在它之前的字母这样做
that let me get this off the screen to
让我把这段视频从屏幕上撤下来
do that I'm going to convert the text of
这样做，我将把文本转换为
paths path object to path and then I'll
路径路径对象到路径，然后我将
ungroup the letters like that and let me
像这样把字母拆开，然后让我
just bring the opacity of that down so I
把它的不透明性降下来，这样我
can see through them a little bit and
能看穿他们一点，
I'm gonna zoom in to zoom in I'm holding
我要放大我手中拿着的
ctrl and rolling up the mouse wheel to
按住Ctrl键并滚动鼠标滚轮以
move the page around I'm just pressing
把书页移来移去我只是在按
down the mouse wheel and moving the
向下移动鼠标滚轮并移动
mouse I'm gonna click this letter
鼠标我要点击这个字母
hold ctrl click and drag it to the right
按住Ctrl键单击并将其拖动到右侧
like that so that it's not quite
就像这样，所以它不完全是
touching the s but pretty close hold
触摸S，但相当接近握住
shift click the other letter bring these
按住Shift键，点击其他字母，带上这些
two over here like that do the same
像这样的两个在这里做同样的事情
thing and that's going to come through
这件事，它会实现的
here and do the same thing with the rest
在这里，对其余的做同样的事情
of this world with the rest of this word
这个世界的其余部分
holding shift while we click on each
在按住Shift键的同时单击每个
letter so it drags the whole word over
字母，所以它拖着整个单词
there this isn't necessarily a step that
在这里，这并不一定是一个步骤
you have to do but I just think the
你必须这样做，但我只是认为
design will look a lot better if you go
如果你走了，设计会看起来好很多
ahead and make these letters look like
并使这些字母看起来像
they fit together so what I'm gonna do
它们合在一起，所以我要做的是
now is I'm gonna duplicate this letter S
现在我要复制这封信S
right here by pressing ctrl D I'm gonna
就在这里，按下Ctrl D键，我将
make that red and then I'll hold shift
把它改成红色，然后我就换班
and click on the letter E and go to path
然后点击字母E并转到Path
difference and if you notice now if you
如果你现在注意到，如果你
move this apart it looks like those two
把这个分开，看起来像是那两个
letters fit with each other so let me
字母彼此契合，所以让我
put that back I'm gonna come through
把它放回去，我会挺过去的
here and do the same thing with the rest
在这里，对其余的做同样的事情
of these letters duplicate that hold
在这些字母中，有两个字母相同
shift click the letter go to path
按住Shift键单击字母转到路径
difference take the letter O ctrl D hold
不同，取字母O ctrl D Hold
shift click the P
按住Shift键并单击P
path difference and I'm sure you get the
路径差异，我相信你会得到
idea by now so so let me go through and
现在有主意了，所以让我先说一遍
do this with the rest of the word here
用这个词的其余部分来做这个
difference I'm actually gonna use the
不同的是，我实际上将使用
keyboard shortcut for this last one
最后一个键盘的快捷键
because I haven't memorized I actually
因为我没有记住我实际上
never used these menus up here I always
我从来没有在这里用过这些菜单
use the keyboard shortcut which for this
为此，请使用键盘快捷键
one is ctrl shift and - okay so let me
一个是Ctrl Shift和-好的，那么让我
take the letter S and hold ctrl and move
拿起字母S，按住Ctrl键移动
that to the right a little bit hold
向右一点拿着
shift click the T move that to the right
按住Shift键并将其向右移动
a little bit while holding ctrl so that
在按住Ctrl键的同时稍作调整，以便
we're locking it onto the horizontal
我们要把它锁在水平线上
axis same thing over here with the R
轴在这里和R轴一样
we're basically we just spacing these
我们基本上只是把这些隔开
letters out apart like that looking good
像这样分开的信件看起来很好
do the same thing over here now let me
在这里做同样的事情，现在让我
zoom back out to see how we're looking
缩小以查看我们的外观
over here okay that's looking pretty
在这里，好的，看起来很漂亮
good right there so what I'm gonna do is
很好，所以我要做的是
I'm gonna unify all those letters
我要把所有这些字母统一起来
together by selecting them all and going
通过选择他们所有人并一起去
to path Union and now what I want to do
走向联合之路，现在我想做的是
is I want to a plot I want to apply a
我想要一个情节，我想要应用一个
perspective like you see here so let me
就像你在这里看到的那样，让我
go to path path effects and you're gonna
转到路径路径效果，您将会
get this path effects editor up here I'm
把这个路径效果编辑器放在这里，我是
gonna click the add path effect button
我将单击添加路径效果按钮
and I'm going to look for perspective
我要去寻找观点
there it is perspective envelope and I
这是透视信封和我
want to check this box that says mere
我想勾选这个框，上面写着
movements in vertical and then grab the
垂直移动，然后抓住
edit pads by nodes tool and what we're
按节点编辑焊盘工具和我们的内容
looking for here we're looking for the
在这里寻找我们正在寻找的
nodes in the corner but they look
角落里的节点，但他们看起来
different they look similar to the other
不同的是，它们看起来很相似
nodes but the look the node that we're
节点，但看起来我们是节点
looking for is white these ones are gray
找的是白色的，这些是灰色的
so they look similar so it's easy to
所以它们看起来很相似，所以很容易
miss them make sure you're grabbing the
想念他们，确保你抓住了
white node like that I'm just going to
像这样的白色节点我正要去
take that and pull that out if you want
如果你想的话，拿着它把它拿出来
you could hold ctrl to lock it onto the
您可以按住Ctrl键将其锁定到
axis pull that out a little bit like
轴线把它拉出来有点像
that just to give it a little bit of a
只是给它一点小小的
perspective and now we can finalize that
视角，现在我们可以最终确定
by going to path object to path now what
通过转到路径对象到路径，现在是什么
I'm gonna do is I'm gonna give this a
我要做的是我要给这个
bit of a 3d effect as you can see here
正如你在这里看到的那样，有点3D效果
if you notice is a bit of a like a 3d
如果你注意到它有点像3D
effect like it's coming out at you like
效果就像它在你身上出现一样
that
那
we're gonna use the extrude feature for
我们将使用挤出功能来
that so let me grab this select tool let
所以让我抓住这个选择工具，让
me just adjust that a little bit make
我只要稍微调整一下就行了
that a little higher that looks pretty
再高一点，看起来很漂亮
good I want to right click this text and
很好，我想用鼠标右键点击这个文本
go to duplicate I want to make this red
去复印，我想把这个改成红色
and I want to hold ctrl and move this up
我想按住Ctrl键并将其上移
above it a little bit I'm gonna hold
在它的上方，我会抱着它
ctrl scale this up a little bit maybe
Ctrl可能会将其放大一点
about that much it doesn't have to be
差不多那么多，不一定非得是
exactly the the amount that I'm scaling
准确地说是我要调整的数量
it you can just eyeball it like
你可以只看它喜欢的样子
doing here and then I want to select
在这里做，然后我想选择
both of these actually let me move this
这两个实际上都让我移动了这个
up a little bit let me select both of
再往上一点，让我选择两个
these and go to extensions generate from
这些并转到扩展名生成自
path and I'm gonna look for extrude and
PATH和我要寻找挤出物和
right here I want to choose polygons and
就在这里，我想选择多边形和
then click apply and it's gonna create
然后单击应用，它将创建
this 3d block right here so let me get
这个3D区块就在这里，让我来
rid of this let me take this new shape
摆脱这个，让我接受这个新的形状
that I created let me ungroup that the
我创建的，让我解开
only unified altogether by going to path
只有通过走上正道才能完全统一
Union and I want to get rid of those
尤尼恩和我想摆脱那些
empty negative spaces in there so I'll
里面空着负数，所以我会
go to path break apart and then path
转到路径拆分，然后转到路径
Union let me get rid of the stroke or
工会让我摆脱中风或者
the outline I'm gonna hold shift and
我要按住Shift键的轮廓和
click on this X up here and let me come
点击这里的这个X，让我来
over here to the fill tab under the HSL
在这里到HSL下的填充选项卡
tab I'm just gonna make sure that a
我只是要确保一个
column is brought all the way up and
柱子一直向上抬起，
then I'll bring the opacity down
然后我会把不透明度降下来
partially like that and now I can take
一部分是这样的，现在我可以
this red text up here our original text
这上面的红色文字是我们的原始文字
make sure it's raised to the top I'm
一定要把它升到最高，我要
gonna click this button raise selection
我要点击此按钮提升选择
to the top select both of these and
在顶部选择这两个选项和
Center them up and they come down here
把它们放在中间，然后它们就下来了
to the alignment menu Center them up on
到对齐菜单，将它们居中
the vertical axis and then align the top
垂直轴，然后将顶部对齐
edges like that so that we end up with
像这样的边缘，所以我们最终得到了
that right there now we could take this
就在那里，我们现在可以把这个
and we can just press delete to get rid
我们只需按Delete键即可删除
of that we don't need that right now so
我们现在不需要那个，所以
now what I want to do is I want to take
现在我想做的是，我想要
this red text this original text layer
此红色文本此原始文本层
and I want to make this white and then I
我想把它变成白色，然后我
want to take the black text beneath it
我想把下面的黑色文本
and I want to apply an offset to it so
我想对它应用一个偏移量
I'm gonna come back up here to the path
我要回到这条小路上
effects menu click the plus button to
效果菜单单击加号按钮以
add a path effect and on this time I'm
加上路径效果，这一次我
looking for offset and I would recommend
正在寻找补偿，我建议
getting familiar getting comfortable
熟悉变得舒适
with this path effect because we'll be
这种路径效应，因为我们将
using this a lot throughout this
在整个过程中经常使用这一点
tutorial where it says offset I'm gonna
教程上面写着偏移量我要
click the plus button to increase the
单击加号按钮以增加
offset and if you notice it's growing a
偏移量，如果你注意到它正在增长
border around the text right there by
文本周围的边框按
default it should have lighter if not
默认情况下，如果不是，它应该有更轻的
just go ahead and select that
只需继续并选择那个
there we go that's looking pretty good
我们走吧，看起来很不错
now let me finalize that by going to
现在让我通过以下几点来结束这一点：
path object to path and now what I want
路径对象到路径，现在是我想要的
to do is I want to create another copy
我要做的是创建另一个副本
of this text here let me show you where
在这篇文章中，让我告诉你
I'm where I'm going with this notice
我带着这张通知要去的地方
this little reflective effect going
这个小小的反射效果
through the text there that's what I'm
通过那里的文字，这就是我
gonna create next so let me take this
接下来要创造，所以让我拿着这个
white text let me duplicate that by
白色文本让我重复这一点
Crescent control-d and I'll just make
新月会控制-d和我只是
this red so I can differentiate it up
这是红色的，所以我能辨别出来。
against the white and I'm going to apply
反对白人，我要申请
an offset to this as well so click on
这也是一个偏移量，所以点击
the offset path effect and where it says
偏移路径效果以及它在哪里显示
offset I'm just going to press - this
偏移量我要按下-这个
time I'm going to click that down maybe
现在我可能要把它按下
not that much right about there is what
并不是说有什么是正确的
we're going for
我们要去的是
again we'll finalize that by going to
再一次，我们将通过以下方式最终确定
path object to path and now I'm going to
Path对象到Path，现在我要
grab the rectangle tool I want to slice
抓起我想要切片的矩形工具
this in half here so I'm gonna use the
这一半在这里，所以我将使用
rectangle tool as a reference point put
将矩形工具作为参考点放置
that through there like that let me just
像这样穿过那里，让我只是
make this green so I can see a little
把这个弄成绿色，这样我就能看得见一点
better okay that looks pretty good let
更好的，好的，看起来很好。
me go to the Select tool and let me
我转到选择工具，让我
adjust that just a little more hold
把那个稍微调整一下
shift click on the rip on the red text
按住Shift键单击红色文本上的裂口
that we have the green box and the red
我们有绿色盒子和红色盒子
text selected and go to path
选定文本并转到路径
intersection so what I'm going to do now
交叉点所以我现在要做的是
is I'm going to color this in so let me
我要给这个上色，所以让我
select all of this and bring the opacity
选择所有这些选项并将不透明度
all the way up to 100% and I'm going to
一直到100%，我要
use the colors depicted here in the
使用此处描述的颜色
thumbnail or something very close anyway
缩略图或其他非常接近的东西
I'm probably not going to get the exact
我可能不会得到确切的
shades but I'll take the other black
墨镜，但我要另一件黑色的
background here and I'm going to make
这里的背景，我要做的是
this a very dark shade of purple like
这是一种很深的紫色，像
that then I'll take the white text in
然后我会将白色文本放入
here I'll make that a light shade of
在这里，我会把它做一个浅色调
purple maybe something with a little
紫色的，可能有一点
more vibrance that looks good maybe
也许看起来更有活力
adjust that a little bit and then I want
稍微调整一下，然后我想
to make this an even lighter shade of
使它成为一个更浅的色调
purple so let me make this something
紫色，让我来做点什么吧
like that down here I actually know this
就像在这里，我其实知道这个
has to be a medium shade of purple my
必须是中等色调的紫色我的
bad okay so we'll do that okay now we're
坏的，好的，我们就这么做，好的，现在我们
going to apply to a gradient to this so
将渐变应用于此，所以
where it says up here in the fill and
上面写着这里的填充物和
stroke menu we're looking for a linear
笔划菜单我们要找的是线性的
gradient click on that grab the gradient
渐变点击，抓取渐变
tool which is right here I just like to
就在这里的工具，我只是喜欢
press G on the keyboard and then take
按键盘上的G键，然后选择
the darker stop and put this towards the
较暗的停止，并将此放置到
top and then take the lighter one and
最上面的，然后拿较轻的那个，然后
put this towards the bottom and I'm
把这个放到底部，我就会
gonna hold ctrl to lock it onto the
按住Ctrl键将其锁定在
vertical axis so that we end up with
垂直轴，所以我们最终得到了
something like that right there now let
就在那里，这样的事情现在让
me go back to the Select tool I want to
我返回到我想要的选择工具
take this text I'm just gonna make this
拿着这条短信，我要把这个
a little lighter I'm just eyeballing
稍微亮一点，我只是在打量
this here I don't
在这里我不知道
like how that looks before so that's
就像以前的样子，所以这就是
looking pretty good right there so
看起来很不错，所以
that's part one we have the text
这是第一部分，我们有文本
finished let me click and drag over all
完成，让我点击并拖动所有内容
of this I want to group it together and
我想把它们组合在一起，
press ctrl G on the keyboard I'm going
按键盘上的Ctrl G键我要走了
to put this off to the side for now
暂时把这件事搁置一边
maybe I'll even scale it down like that
也许我甚至会把它缩小成那样
hold ctrl and scale it down and now
按住Ctrl键并按比例缩小，现在
we're going to create the emblem so let
我们要制作会徽，所以让我们
me grab the actually first let me show
我先拿着，让我展示一下
you the thumbnail here I'm gonna create
你就是我要创建的缩略图
this emblem that you see in the
你看到的这个徽章
background to create that shape I'm
创建该形状的背景我正在
actually going to start off with this
实际上，我们要从这个开始
square so let me show you how that works
方块，让我向你展示它是如何工作的
I'm going to grab this squares and
我要拿着这个方块
rectangles tool I'm gonna hold ctrl +
矩形工具我要按住Ctrl+组合键
Shift + click and drag on the cabbage to
按住Shift键并在卷心菜上单击并拖动
create a perfectly symmetrical square
创建一个完美对称的正方形
like that I just want to come up here to
就像这样，我只是想来这里
where it says make Carter corner sharp
上面写着让卡特的角尖
make sure that's enabled if you can't
如果不能，请确保启用该选项
click it and it's grayed out that means
点击它，它就会灰显，这意味着
you're good to go
你可以走了
we don't want rounded corners for we're
我们不想要圆角，因为我们
about to do here so it's important to
即将在这里完成所以重要的是
check that and let me convert that to a
检查一下，让我将其转换为
path by going to path object to path and
路径：转到路径对象到路径，然后
I'll go to the nodes tool and I want to
我将转到节点工具，然后我想
add some new nodes in here I want to add
在此处添加一些我想要添加的新节点
one right here and add one right there
这里加一个，那里加一个
so let me select those nodes click this
所以让我选择这些节点，点击这个
button up here to the top left that says
左上角的按钮，上面写着
insert new nodes into selected segments
将新节点插入选定的线段
and then come down here do the same
然后下来做同样的事情
thing and then I want to select these
然后我想选择这些
two nodes right here the two new ones
两个节点就在这里，两个新的
and up here where it says show
在上面写着表演的地方
transformation handles for selected
所选对象的变换句柄
nodes let's go ahead and turn that on so
节点，让我们继续打开它，这样
we can see the transformation because we
我们可以看到这种转变，因为我们
want to do is we want to hold ctrl down
我们想要做的是按住Ctrl键
and just hold ctrl and shift actually
实际上只需按住Ctrl和Shift
and just scale them out like that pull
然后像这样把它们向外拉
them out about that far that's looking
他们在看着他们走了那么远
pretty good
挺不错的
and now I want to take these bottom ones
现在我想把下面这几个
down here and hold ctrl and just scale
在这里按住Ctrl键，然后进行缩放
those down actually let me hold ctrl and
那些向下的实际上让我按住Ctrl键并
shift then I'll hold ctrl and move this
按下Shift键，然后按住Ctrl键并移动它
up like that that right there is what
就像那样，就在那里有什么
we're looking for that's sort of it's
我们在找，这是一种
kind of like a squared shield kind of
有点像正方形的盾牌
shape now once you're done making that
一旦你做好了，现在就塑造
shape you can go ahead and disable this
Shape您可以继续并禁用此选项
transformation handle because the next
转换句柄，因为下一个
time you go to Newton use the nodes tool
转到牛顿时使用结点工具
that will get in your way if you don't
如果你不这样做，那会妨碍你的
need it so I like to always turn that
我需要它，所以我喜欢总是把它
off when I'm done now let me take this
当我做完的时候，现在让我拿着这个
and scale this up a little bit let me
把这个放大一点，让我
take the text actually and I'm gonna
把文本拿来，我就会
raise this to the top and place it over
把这个举到上面，然后放在上面
the emblem here let me Center them up on
这里的徽章让我把注意力集中在他们身上
the vertical
垂直的
horizontal-axis like that I'm gonna take
像这样的横轴，我要
just the text and hold ctrl and shift
只显示文本并按住Ctrl和Shift
and scale this up like that and I want
像这样扩大规模，我想
to take the shield right here and I want
在这里拿到盾牌，我想
to make it the same color as this dark
把它做成和这个深色一样的颜色
purple down here so I'm gonna grab the
这里是紫色的，所以我要拿起
dropper which is over here we can just
滴管，在这里，我们可以
press D on the keyboard there you go and
按键盘上的D键，就可以了
now I want to create these little accent
现在我想创造出这些小小的口音
pieces going on the inside of that
碎片在它的内部
shield shape so to do that I'm going to
盾牌形状所以为了做到这一点，我要
create a duplicate of this object I'm
创建此对象的副本我正在
going to right click and go to duplicate
转至右键单击并转至复制
and I'm going to make this the lighter
我要把这个做得更轻
shade of purple so let me grab the
紫色的阴影，所以让我抓住
dropper again press D on the keyboard
Dropper再次按键盘上的D键
and use this lighter shade as a
用这个较浅的色调作为
reference there we go back to the Select
参考这里，我们回到精选
tool and now I want to do another offset
工具，现在我想再做一次补偿
so let me add a new path effect we're
所以让我添加一个新的路径效应，我们
gonna use offset again and I'm going to
我将再次使用偏移量，我将
use the - I'm going to shrink this down
用-我要把这个缩小一下
like that and what I'm paying attention
就像这样，我注意到了什么
to here is I want to make sure that the
到这里来是我想确保
thickness here this the padding between
厚度这里这个之间的填充物
the dark and the light here is pretty
这里的黑暗和光明都很美
much the same or close anyway to the
大致相同或无论如何都接近
thickness of the wording here I want the
这里的措辞粗细我要的是
I want the padding to be consistent
我想让填充物保持一致
between the shield and the text so you
在盾牌和文本之间，所以你
may have to tweak that manually I'm not
可能需要手动调整，我不是
using exact measurements or anything I'm
使用精确的测量或任何我正在使用的
just going by how it looks on my screen
只是看看它在我屏幕上的样子
that's good enough so let me go to path
这就够了，让我去PATH吧
object to path and now what I'll do is
反对PATH，现在我要做的是
I'll create a duplicate of this
我将创建一个副本
right-click it go to duplicate and I'm
右键单击它，转到复制，我是
just gonna make this a different color
我要把它改成不同的颜色
for now maybe red bring the opacity down
就目前而言，红色可能会降低不透明度
it doesn't matter what color it is let
它是什么颜色的并不重要
me hold ctrl and shift and scale this
我按住Ctrl键和Shift键并进行缩放
down to make it smaller and then I'll go
把它弄小，然后我就走
back to the nodes tool up here select
返回到此处的节点工具，选择
these two nodes right here and then turn
这两个节点就在这里，然后转
the transformation handles back on and
转换将重新启动，并
then hold ctrl and shift and scale these
然后按住Ctrl键和Shift键并对其进行缩放
nodes up like that so that they surpass
节点像那样上升，这样它们就超过了
so that they extend beyond the the white
所以它们延伸到了白色之外
via the lighter purple shape there which
通过那里较浅的紫色形状
is what we're going for
就是我们要做的事
let me turn those off go back to the
让我把它们关掉，回到
Select tool hold shift click on the
选择工具按住Shift键并单击
other shape so we have them both
其他形状，所以我们两个都有
selected and go to path difference and
选择并转到路径差异和
now we want them to be two different
现在我们希望他们是两个不同的人
colors so I'm going to go to path break
颜色，所以我要去小路休息
apart to break them apart and
把它们分开，然后
separate pieces paths break apart and
单独的片段路径被分开并
let me click off of that to deselect
让我单击该选项以取消选择
everything I'm gonna take this one right
一切我都要把这件事做好
here and make this the medium shade of
在这里，让这个成为中等色调的
purple which is right here so let me
紫色，就在这里，所以让我
grab the dropper again just press D on
再次抓住滴管只需按下D键即可
the keyboard and just click on that and
键盘，只需点击即可
there to give that that same color maybe
可能会有同样的颜色
a little lighter there we go
我们要走了，稍微轻松一点
I'll grab the select tool take this text
我会抓起选择工具，取下这段文字
item raise it to the top once again and
再一次把它举到顶部，然后
as you can see we are on our way we just
如你所见，我们正在路上，我们只是
have to now create the controller
现在必须创建控制器
illustration so let me bring that in
插图，所以让我把它带进来
here as you can see now now we're going
就像你现在看到的，我们现在要走了
to create the controller the shape of
创建形状为的控制器
this controller is a very unique shape
这个控制器的形状非常独特
there's no tool that makes that specific
没有任何工具可以使这一点变得具体
shape and Inkscape so we're gonna
形状和墨迹所以我们要
manually create it using ellipses so let
使用省略号手动创建它，以便让
me move that off the screen we can do
我把它从屏幕上移走，我们可以
now is you can take this and just hold
现在你可以拿着这个，拿着
ctrl and shift to scale that down put it
按Ctrl键和Shift键缩小比例
off to the side for now may be a good
暂时靠边站可能是个不错的选择
idea to save your work at this point in
此时保存您的工作的想法
case Inkscape crashes you don't want to
Case Inkscape崩溃，你不想
lose all of this that you've been
丢掉你一直以来的一切
working on so I'm actually gonna do that
所以我真的要这么做了
real quick myself okay so now that I've
我自己真的很快，好的，现在我已经
saved my work let's create the
保存我的工作让我们创建
controller now so I'm gonna grab the
控制器现在，所以我要抓起
circles and ellipses tool I'm gonna
圆圈和省略号工具我要
click and drag to create an ellipse like
单击并拖动以创建类似于的椭圆
that and while I'm creating this shape
当我创造这个形状的时候
I'm just gonna for now make this black
我现在只想把它改成黑色
and I'm gonna make sure the opacity is
我要确保不透明度是
down in half like that because we're
像这样一分为二因为我们
gonna be able to see through these
就能看穿这些东西
shapes I'm going to convert this to a
形状我要将其转换为
path by going to path object to path and
路径：转到路径对象到路径，然后
then I'm gonna grab the edit pads by
然后我会拿起编辑板
nodes tool and I want to take these two
Nodes Tool和我想把这两个
nodes up here and hold ctrl and just
节点位于此处并按住Ctrl键，然后
scale them up like that not too much
像这样放大，不要太大
maybe up about that much and then I'll
可能会涨那么多，然后我会
take this node and hold ctrl and scale
使用此节点并按住Ctrl和Scale
that down a little bit now let me grab
放低一点，现在让我拿一下
this select tool I'm gonna make this a
这个精选工具我要把它变成
little wider again I'm just eyeballing
再宽一点，我只是在盯着看
us it doesn't have to be exactly like
我们并不一定要完全像
what you see on my screen just something
你在我的屏幕上看到的只是
there abouts is pretty good I'm gonna
这些都很好，我要
click on this so I get the rotation
点击这个，这样我就可以轮换了
handles I'm gonna hold ctrl to take this
把手我要按住Ctrl键来拿这个
little hand on the top right corner and
右上角的小手
I'm gonna rotate this clockwise one to
我要把这个顺时针旋转到
two steps like that
这样的两个步骤
now let me duplicate that by pressing
现在让我重复一下，按下
ctrl D I want to flip this horizontally
Ctrl D我想水平翻转这个
and hold ctrl and move this over here
按住Ctrl键，然后把这个移到这里
like that and now I want to grab the
就像这样，现在我想抓住
ellipses tool again and I want to create
再次使用椭圆工具，我想创建
another ellipse
另一个椭圆
going through the inside here like this
像这样穿透这里的内部
make sure that this is oops make sure
确保这是OOPS确保
this is going through to the other side
这就是通向另一边
like that that's looking pretty good now
像这样，现在看起来很不错
I just want to make sure that these
我只想确保这些
three shapes are spaced apart evenly
三个形状均匀地隔开
otherwise you'll get a little bit of
否则你会得到一点
asymmetry here so let me select all
这里不对称，所以让我选择全部
three of those and down here in the
三个这样的人，然后在这里
align and distribute menu and under the
“对齐和分布”菜单下的
distribute panel you should see
您应该看到的分布式面板
something that says make horizontal gaps
一些写着在水平方向上产生空隙的东西
between objects equal go ahead and click
对象之间相等，请继续并单击
on that and now we can unify this
现在我们可以统一这一点
together by going to path Union and we
通过去Path Union和我们一起
have the beginning of a controller shape
具有控制器形状的开头
but if you notice it's not quite there
但如果你注意到它并不完全在那里
yet if you notice on the thumbnail here
不过，如果你注意到这里的缩略图
the controller shape dips down like that
控制器形状像这样向下倾斜
and then it dips upward like that so to
然后它像这样向上倾斜，所以
do that we're gonna have to manually
要做到这一点，我们将不得不手动
create that shape so let me grab the
创建该形状，让我来获取
Edit path by nodes tool again and I'm
再次使用节点工具编辑路径，我将
gonna take this note up here I'm gonna
我要把这张纸条拿上来，我要
click and drag this down actually
实际上，点击并将其向下拖动
there's two nodes there's one cigar grab
有两个节点，有一个雪茄抓斗
both of those let me undo that with ctrl
这两个选项都允许我使用Ctrl键来撤消
Z if you end up having two nodes there
Z如果最终在那里有两个节点
like I do just click and drag over both
就像我一样，只需在两者上单击并拖动
of those and combine them together join
并将它们结合在一起
selected nodes there we go and then hold
我们在那里选择节点，然后保持不变
ctrl and just click and drag them down
按住Ctrl键并单击并向下拖动它们
like that and then just take this handle
像这样，然后拿着这个把手
and make it adjust it so that it's this
然后让它调整一下，这样就是这样
line right here is going flush with the
就在这里，这条线与
rest of it don't worry about this side
剩下的就不用担心这边了
we're actually gonna exclude this side
我们实际上要把这一边排除在外
and duplicate this left side let's take
然后复制左边的这个，我们来看看
this one and do the same thing move this
这一个，做同样的事情，移动这个
up here like that adjust this handle
像这样往上调这个把手
there we go now what I want to do is
好了，现在我想做的是
hold ctrl and click on that node so that
按住Ctrl键并单击该节点，以便
it makes it automatically smooth I want
它使它自动平滑，我想要的
to do the same thing up here hold ctrl
要在此处执行相同的操作，请按住Ctrl键
click on this node I'm actually gonna
点击这个节点，我实际上要
bring this up a little more there we go
把这个再提起来一点，我们开始了
now what I want to do is I want to
现在我想做的是我想要
temporarily turn on snapping where it
暂时打开捕捉位置
says enable snapping turn that on and
表示启用捕捉打开该选项，然后
over here where it says we're gonna want
在这里，上面写着我们会想要
this one that says snap to custom nodes
这个选项显示为捕捉到自定义节点
and then this one that says snap to
然后这张上面写着对齐
smooth nodes and I'm gonna grab the
光滑的结节，我要抓起
Bezier pen over here or you could press
贝塞尔钢笔在这里，或者你可以按
B on the keyboard I'm gonna snap to that
B在键盘上，我会抓住它
middle node that we just created and
我们刚刚创建的中间节点和
click and then bring the line straight
单击，然后将线条拉直
down to the other node click on that and
向下到另一个节点，单击该节点，然后
then finish this shape up going around
然后完成这个形状的旋转
the outside of the controller here and
控制器的外部在这里和
that
那
the starting point now I want to grab
现在我想抓住的起点
this select tool hold shift click on the
此选择工具按住Shift键并单击
controller and go to path difference and
控制器，并转到路径差和
now we have half of a controller so what
现在我们有了半个控制器，那又怎么样
I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是我要
duplicate that right click go to
复制单击鼠标右键转到
duplicate flip it horizontally and then
复制水平翻转它，然后
snap it on to the left side over here so
把它扣在左边，这样就可以
that we end up with this symmetrical
我们最终得到了这个对称的
shape now let me turn off the snapping
Shape Now让我关闭捕捉
now so that it doesn't get in the way
现在，这样它就不会妨碍你
for the rest of the way and I want to
在接下来的旅程中，我想
click and drag over both of those and go
在这两个选项上单击并拖动，然后继续
to path Union and we now have our
我们现在有了我们的
controller shape so now it's time to add
控制器形状，所以现在是添加
some buttons and some some simulated
一些按钮和一些模拟按钮
lighting effects in here a little bit of
这里的灯光效果有一点
shading and some buttons so to do that
阴影和一些按钮来实现这一点
let's first add these buttons down here
让我们先把这些按钮添加到下面
grab the circles and ellipses tool hold
抓起圆形和椭圆形刀柄
ctrl and shift create a perfectly round
Ctrl和Shift键可创建完美的圆形
circle put that right there and then I
圆圈把它放在那里，然后我
want to duplicate that by pressing ctrl
我想通过按Ctrl来复制它
D instead of right-clicking and going to
D而不是单击鼠标右键并转到
duplicate we're just going to press ctrl
复制，我们只需按Ctrl键
D just easier to do that make this red
I‘把这个改成红色就更容易了
scale that down and now I want to take
缩小规模，现在我想要
both of those and group them together
并将它们组合在一起
and I want to duplicate that by pressing
我想通过按下
ctrl D again hold ctrl and click and
再次按住Ctrl D并单击，然后
drag these over here so that we have a
把这些拖到这里来，这样我们就有一个
copy over here and again we want to make
一遍又一遍地复制我们想要复制的
sure that this is centered up on the
当然，这是集中在
controller so let's group those together
控制器，让我们将它们组合在一起
with that group button up there hold
用上面那个组按钮按住
shift click on the controller and then
按住Shift键单击控制器，然后
again just make sure they're centered up
再说一次，只要确保它们居中
on the vertical axis like that I might
在这样的垂直轴上，我可能会
even make these a little bigger bring
甚至把这些做大一点也会带来
them down a little more okay that looks
再往下放一点，看起来不错
pretty good
挺不错的
now I'm gonna ungroup those actually no
现在我要把那些实际上不是的
there we go this is the ungroup button
我们开始了，这是解组按钮
because it's grouped several layers deep
因为它被分成了好几层深
so we'll have to do like a deep ungroup
所以我们将不得不像深度解组一样
create the D pad over here and the
在这里创建D Pad，然后
buttons over here so let me grab the
纽扣在这里，让我拿一下
squares and rectangles tool zoom back in
正方形和矩形工具放大
just create a very simple very simple
只需创建一个非常简单非常简单的
rectangle like that let me zoom in I'm
像这样的长方形让我放大我是
gonna use this little rounded node at
我将使用这个圆角的小节点
the top right to make this to make the
右上角将此设置为使
edges of that rounded and then I'll take
它的边缘是圆形的，然后我要
this note up here and bring that in life
这张纸条放在这里，把它带到生活中
like that so that we end up with
就像这样，这样我们就会得到
slightly rounded rectangle a slightly
略微圆角的长方形
rounded rectangle like that right click
像右击那样圆角矩形
that go to duplicate and then we're just
去复制，然后我们就
gonna rotate that 90 degrees with this
用这个把它旋转90度
button that says rotate selection 90
显示旋转选择90的按钮
degrees clockwise there we go I actually
顺时针方向，我们走到那里，我实际上
don't like how that button how this came
我不喜欢那个按钮这是怎么来的
out so emotionally to delete that I'm
如此感情用事地删除了我
going to grab the nodes tool this is a
要获取节点工具，这是一个
little too elongated so I'm going to
有点太长了，所以我要
convert this to a path path object to
将其转换为路径路径对象
path this is all optional you don't have
路径这都是可选的，您没有
to do it what i'm doing here i'm just
去做我在这里做的事，我只是
being meticulous at this point i'm gonna
在这一点上，我将一丝不苟地
take those nodes bring them up a little
拿起这些节点，把它们抬高一点
bit with the arrow keys and i'll do the
用箭头键敲击，我会做
same thing again control d rotate it 90
同样的事情再次控制d旋转它90
degrees and that looks a little better
学位，这样看起来好一点
i'll just go with that select both of
我就选这两个吧。
them go to path Union now let me just
他们现在去PATH UNION，让我
scale that down a little bit put that
把它缩小一点把它放在
right here now I want to put a little
现在我想在这里放一点
circle behind this but behind this as
圈在这个后面，但在这个后面是
well if I bring this back in you'll
好吧，如果我把这个带回来，你会
notice there's a circle behind the d-pad
注意，D-Pad后面有一个圆圈
and a circle behind the button so let me
按钮后面还有一个圆圈，所以让我
create a circle control and shift to
创建圆形控件并按Shift键
make a perfectly round circle I'm going
做一个完美的圆圈我要走了
to make this it's gonna make this green
为了让它变得更绿
for now layer this beneath the d-pad
现在把这个放在D-Pad下面
with the button up here that says lower
上面有个按钮，上面写着降低
selection one step hold shift click on
选择一步按住Shift键并单击
that and just make sure to Center it up
只要确保把它放在中心位置
on the vertical and horizontal axis like
在垂直轴和水平轴上，如
that I'll move this up here I'm gonna
我要把这个搬到这里来我要
make this a little bigger then I'll take
把这个做大一点，然后我就买了
this green circle duplicate that by
这个绿色的圆圈通过以下方式复制
pressing control D and hold ctrl to move
按住Control D键并按住Ctrl键可移动
this over here and now we can create
在这里，现在我们可以创造
some buttons so let me create more
一些按钮，让我创建更多按钮
circles over here ctrl and shift I'll
在这里转一圈Ctrl和Shift我会
make that red I just want to Center this
把那个改成红色，我只想把这个放在中间
up make sure it's centered within the
向上，确保它位于
circle there take this circle control D
那里的圆圈控制这个圆圈D
to duplicate it bring this one down here
要复制它，请将这个带到这里来
shift-click both of them and then group
按住Shift键并同时单击它们，然后分组
them together ctrl D to duplicate click
它们一起按住Ctrl D以复制单击
on it again to get the rotation handles
再次放在上面以获得旋转手柄
and then hold ctrl and rotate this
然后按住Ctrl键并旋转这个
counter or clockwise rather until you
逆时针或顺时针，直到你
end up with buttons going in all four
结果四个按钮都有了
directions like that and that's what
像这样的方向，这就是
we're looking for so let me hold shift
我们正在寻找，所以让我按住轮班
and click on both of those I want to
然后点击我想要的两个选项
group them together
将它们组合在一起
shift-click on the circle and center
按住Shift键并单击圆和中心
that up within the circle and the
在圆圈和圆圈内
vertical and horizontal axis and what
垂直轴和水平轴等
I'm gonna do now is now that we have our
我现在要做的就是现在我们有了
buttons in place I want to add I want to
按钮就位我想添加我想要
add some more details in here so first
在这里添加更多细节，所以首先
let me just click and drag over all of
我只需点击并拖动所有
this and do a deep on a group let me
这让我对一群人做了一个深入的了解
just make sure everything is ungrouped
只要确保所有东西都未分组即可
here and now what I'm going to do is I'm
此时此刻我要做的是
going to let's click and drag over
接下来，让我们点击并拖动到
everything let's bring the opacity all
一切，让我们带来不透明的一切
the way up like that let's take the
像这样往上走，让我们走
controller and make this the medium
控制器，并将其作为媒介
shade of purple which is over here grab
紫色的阴影，在这里抓住
press D on the keyboard to grab the
按键盘上的D键可抓取
dropper there we go go back to the
水滴在那里，我们要回到
Select tool I want to make this I want
选择我想要的工具，我想要
to make these black circles the same
为了让这些黑圈变得一样
shade as well so I'm gonna press D to
阴影也一样，所以我要按D键
get the dropper back to the Select tool
将滴管放回选择工具
D for the dropper there we go and now I
D为了滴管，我们走了，现在我
want to go back to the Select tool I
想要返回到选择工具I
want to take this D pad these joysticks
我想拿这个D垫和这些操纵杆
over here and these buttons and make
在这里和这些按钮，并使
them the same shade as a dark purple
它们的色调与深紫色相同
here so let me shift click all of that
在这里，让我移动一下，点击所有这些
I'm gonna make sure I have all of that
我要确保我拥有所有这些
selected and then I'll come over here
被选中，然后我会来这里
and again D for the dropper and make
再一次D代表滴管和Make
this the dark shade of purple like that
这是深紫色，像那样
that's what I'm going for it
这就是我要做的
and now back to the select tool let's
现在回到选择工具，让我们
take this green shape hold shift grab
拿着这个绿色形状的按住换挡抓具
this green shape hold shift grab this
这个绿色的形状按住Shift抓住这个
circle down here and then this circle
在这里转一圈，然后再转这一圈
down here as well and make this the
在这里也是如此，并使这成为
light shade of purple so once again
再一次淡淡的紫色
press D on the keyboard to grab the
按键盘上的D键可抓取
dropper there we go and now we have that
水滴，我们走了，现在我们有了
colored in the final part of the
在最后部分涂上颜色
controller here is to add these little
这里的控制器是添加这些小的
these little shading these little this
这些小小的阴影这些小小的
little shading effect here so let me
这里有一点阴影效果，所以让我
take this controller object right here
将这个控制器对象放在这里
I want to duplicate that by pressing
我想通过按键复制这一点
control D I want to make this green or
控制D我想让它变成绿色或
whatever color you want just some kind
你想要什么颜色，只要一种就行。
of contrasting color I want to bring the
对比色，我想要带上
opacity down like that and once again
像这样降低不透明度，然后再一次
we're going to use the offset path
我们将使用偏移路径
effect so I'm going to add a new path
效果，所以我要添加一条新路径
effect right back to offset over here
效果立即返回到这里进行偏移
and where it says offset I'm just gonna
在上面写着抵消的地方，我只是想
use this minus symbol make this a little
用这个减号让这个有点
smaller like that
像那样小一点
that's what we're looking for now let me
这就是我们要找的，现在让我
finalise that I actually make it a
最后，我真的把它变成了
little smaller
小一点
now let me finalise that by going to
现在让我通过以下几点来结束这一点：
path object to path and then let me
将对象路径到路径，然后让我
duplicate this by pressing ctrl D and
按Ctrl D并复制此命令
I'll make this red and I'm just going to
我会把它染成红色的，我只是要
move this up up like this I'm gonna hold
把这个像这样往上移，我要拿着
ctrl and just scale that up a little bit
Ctrl键，然后稍微放大一点
when I'm paying attention to here is the
当我注意到这里是
little piece that's extending from
一小块从
little green piece that's extending from
一小块绿色的东西从
underneath the red object here that's
在红色物体下面，这是
gonna make up the lighting effect so I'm
我要把灯光效果补上，所以我
gonna go with I'm gonna go with the
我要走了，我要走了
positioning like that hold shift click
像按住Shift键点击那样定位
on the green object and go to path
在绿色对象上，然后转到路径
difference so now I just want to keep
所以现在我只想保持
this object here I want to get rid of
我想扔掉这里的这个物体
this so let me break them apart by going
所以让我来把他们分开
to path break apart click off of it to
要断开路径，请单击将其关闭到
deselect everything and just take this
取消选择所有内容，就拿着这个
and get rid of it I'm gonna take this
把它处理掉，我要拿着这个
object bring the opacity all the way up
对象将不透明度调高到最高
and make this the same color that this
把这个做成和这个一样的颜色
is right here so once again we're
就在这里所以我们再一次
grabbing the dropper tool press D on the
抓起滴管工具，按D键
keyboard make that the same color and
键盘使其具有相同颜色和
now I could just duplicate this object
现在我可以复制这个对象
ctrl D flip it horizontally and then
Ctrl D水平翻转它，然后
just place it over here on the other
把它放在这边的另一头
side like that and then finally I'm
像这样的一边，然后我终于
gonna put one more piece right here so
我要在这里再放一块，所以
let me duplicate this object again make
让我再复制一次这个对象
this green bring the opacity down and
这种绿色降低了不透明度，
come back over here to the path effects
回到这里来看看路径效果
menu and add another offset bring this
菜单并添加另一个偏移量，从而实现以下功能
down right about there roughly the same
就在那里，大体相同
as we did before finalize that by going
就像我们之前做的那样，通过
to path object to path and then I want
将对象路径到路径，然后我希望
to duplicate this control D turn this
要复制此控件D，请旋转此
red and then I'm just gonna take this
红色的，然后我就拿着这个
bottom arrow and click and drag that
向下箭头，然后单击并拖动
down like this and I'm going to hold
像这样倒下，我要坚持住
ctrl and bring this up here like that
按住Ctrl键，然后像这样把这个拿到这里来
and again when I'm paying attention to
再一次当我注意到
is right here this little green part
就在这里，这个绿色的小部分
that's it's excluded from the rest of it
那就是它被排除在它的其余部分之外
I'm gonna hold shift click on the green
我要按住Shift键点击绿色
object so we haven't both selected and
对象，所以我们没有同时选择和
go to path difference and then we can go
去路径差，然后我们就可以走了
to path break apart hold shift and click
要断开路径，请按住Shift键并单击
on this little piece right here to
在这里的这一小块上
deselect it though we only have these
取消选择它，尽管我们只有这些
two pieces selected then I could press
选择两件，然后我就可以按
Delete on the keyboard to get rid of
在键盘上删除要去掉的
them
他们
and now I want to take this object bring
现在我想把这个物体带到
the opacity up and once again we're
不透明度提高了，我们又一次
grabbing the dropper and making that the
抓住滴管，让它成为
same shade so okay so now the controller
同样的色调，所以好的，现在控制器
is finished we have all of our
已经完成了我们所有的
individual objects finished I'm going to
单件物品完成，我要去
click and drag over everything over the
单击并将所有内容拖到
controller rather group it together
控制器宁可将其组合在一起
let's bring it over here I'm gonna hold
让我们把它带到这里来，我要拿着
ctrl and shift and scale it down it's
Ctrl和Shift并按比例缩小它
time to put everything together now the
现在是时候把一切都放在一起了
place that's right over here I'm sizing
就在这里，我正在调整大小
it up so that it fits within here nicely
把它抬起来，这样它就能很好地放在这里
but then the top parts of the controller
但然后控制器的顶部部分
are expanding beyond the emblem they're
正在超越他们的徽章
just a little bit not by much but just a
只是一点点，不是很多，只是
little bit and one thing out one more
一点一点，一件事再多一件
thing I want to do for the controller
我想为控制器做的事情
here if you notice I have a little bit
在这里，如果你注意到我有一点
of a I have some padding going around
当然，我有一些垫子。
the controller so I want to do that as
控制器，所以我想这样做
well I want to add some padding around
好的，我想加一些填充物。
there first let me Center it up with the
首先让我把它放在中心位置
idiot with the emblem here I'm gonna
带着徽章的笨蛋，我要
hold shift and click on the emblem and
按住Shift键并单击徽标，然后
just make sure it's centered up on the
只要确保它在中心位置
vertical axis like that now I can click
像这样的垂直轴，现在我可以点击
on the controller let's ungroup it click
在控制器上，我们将其解组，然后单击
off at the deselect let's take the
在取消选择处下车，让我们来看看
controller shape right here duplicate
控制器形状就在此处复制
that by pressing ctrl D I want to make
通过按Ctrl D键，我想要制作
this the same shade as the dark purple
这是和深紫色一样的颜色
here let me just grab the dropper tool
现在，让我拿起滴管工具
by pressing D make that the same color
按D键使其颜色相同
back to the select tool and now I'm just
回到选择工具，现在我只是
going to lower this until it goes
我要把这个放下来，直到它消失
beneath the controller there so I'm
在控制器下面，所以我
gonna lower it one step at a time until
我会一步一步地把它放低直到
it goes beneath the controller there we
它放在控制器下面，我们在那里
go and then we'll add an offset and path
继续，然后我们将添加一个偏移量和路径
effect offset and I'm going to increase
效果抵消，我要增加
this offset and again what I'm paying
这一补偿，以及我所支付的
attention to here is the thickness of
注意这里的厚度是
this padding making sure it's consistent
这种填充物确保了它的一致性
with the thickness of this padding and
对于这种衬垫的厚度和
this padding over here we want
这块垫子是我们要的
everything to look nice and consistent
所有的东西看起来都很漂亮和一致
like it all belongs together nice fluid
就像它属于所有人一样，很好的液体
looking there we go
看着那里，我们走了
now let me go to path object to path to
现在，让我转到路径对象到路径
finalize that and let me just take all
最后敲定，让我把所有的东西都拿走
of this right here the whole controller
就在这里，整个控制器
with the padding and just group it all
使用填充物，然后将其全部分组
together
在一起
there we go I'm just gonna scale it down
我们走吧，我要把它缩小
a little bit we just double-check make
有一点我们只是复核了一下
sure I have it centered there we go
当然，我把它放在中心，我们走
so we have the design finished for the
所以我们已经完成了
most part I'm actually gonna make the
实际上，大部分时间我都会让
text a little larger there we go
文本稍微大一点，我们开始了
you may have to adjust the sizing based
您可能需要根据需要调整大小
on how your design came out I'm just
关于你的设计是怎么出来的，我只是
gonna manually tweak this a little bit
我要手动调整一下这个
the final part now would be to add this
现在的最后一部分是添加这个
yellow outline going around the entire
黄色轮廓环绕整个
design just to tie everything together
设计只是为了将一切联系在一起
so to do that let's take everything
所以要做到这一点，让我们拿走一切
let's press control D on the keyboard to
让我们按键盘上的控制D，
duplicate everything and let's do a deep
复制所有内容，让我们做一个深入的
on group click the ungroup button a few
在群组中单击几下取消群组按钮
times to make sure it's all ungrouped
时间确保一切都未分组
and go to path Union and now I'm gonna
然后去联合路，现在我要去
make this yellow because it contrasts
把这个变成黄色是因为它形成鲜明对比
nicely with the purple there and I want
紫色很好，我想要
to send this to the bottom where it says
将其发送到底部，上面写着
lower selection to the bottom and then
将选择降低到底部，然后
finally one last time we will add an
最后一次我们将添加一个
offset path effect so but by this point
抵消路径效应，但此时
I'm sure you're pretty familiar with
我相信你非常熟悉
this path effect we're just gonna add
我们要添加的路径效应
this in manually like that that right
这个在手动就像那个对
there looks pretty good now we can just
现在看起来很好我们可以
finalize this by going to path object to
通过将对象路径到来完成此操作
path and there you go we are finished
路径，就这样，我们完成了
with this tutorial there you have your
通过本教程，您可以获得
eSports logo design made with Inkscape
使用Inkscape制作的电子竞技标志设计
so if you have any questions leave a
因此，如果您有任何问题请留下
comment below and as always thanks for
下面评论，一如既往地感谢
watching
看
[Music]
[音乐]